## Nonie Fulo Lacra

#### Software Engineer

Searching for favorable career opportunities that would assist me in gaining greater practical excellence in the software engineer industry where I can put my analytical and technical skills to contribute to the growth of the organization. Comes with 2 years of work experience as a Technical Support and 2 years as a Research Editor.

monielacra@gmail.com

Brgy, Ramon Magsaysay, Quezon city, Philippines

github.com/NonieLacra

09663803783

30 August, 1999

NonieLacra

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Research Editor**ADT Market Research Services

06/2016 - 03/2018

Unit 102-103 One Lourdes Place #126 Road 1, Bagong Pag-asa, Ouezon City

#### Tasks

- Product Quality Assurance
- Research Editor
- Field Researcher

Contact: Ofelia Tamondong Maglalang - 09258163254

#### **Customer Service Representative**

Concentrix - Shaw

08/2020 - Present

Shaw Blvd, Mandaluyong, 1552 Metro Manila

#### Tasks

- Chat Support
- Technical Support
- Customer Service

Contact: Jennelyn Chiu-Delfin - 09205656383

#### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

Freight Management System: Administrative (Facility Reservation, Visitor Management, Legal Management and Document Management) (01/2022 - 04/2022)

- A Capstone Project who achieved the Best Research Presentation among BSIT Department
- Scrum Master and Head Programmer of the Team
- Awarded as 2nd Best Presenter in the Annual Multidisciplinary Research Festival at Bestlink College of the Philippines

#### **EDUCATION**

### Tertiary

#### Bestlink College of the Philippines

06/2018 - 07/2022

#1071 Brgy, Kaligayahan, Quirino Highway, Novaliches, Quezon City

#### Course

 Graduate of Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Major in Information Security

#### **SKILLS**



#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

# 1st Runner-up at 3RD SIMP-AAG-BCP Multidisciplinary Research Festival (06/2022 - 07/2022)

Scrum Master of our Team, Annual Research Festival held by Singapore Institute of Multidisciplinary Professions, Ascendens Asia and Bestlink College of the Philippines

#### Top Agent of the Month (05/2022 - 06/2022)

Top Agent of the Monthh Awardee by Concentrix Shaw

Top Agent of the 3rd Quarter 2022 (07/2021 - 09/2021)
Top Agent of the 3rd Quarter Awardee by Concentrix Shaw

2nd Place in Short Film Making (10/2019 - 11/2019) Short Film Director, Bestlink of the Philippines

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Certificate of Recognition - 3RD SIMP-AAG-BCP Multidisciplinary Research Festival (06/2022 - 07/2022) Bestlink College of the Philippines

Certificate of Participation - Student Research Seminar and Workshop (05/2022 - 06/2022)

Bestlink College of the Philippines

Certificate of Graduation - School of Discipleship 1, 2 and 3 (02/2018 - 03/2019)

Amazing Hope Worship and Training Center

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Filipino

Full Professional Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Community Sevice Cooking Traveling

Gaming | Video and Image Editing

Programming